So my presentation was about why
decentralized identity, first-person
identity as I like to call it, needs a
legal foundation. And I spoke to the idea
that SEDI, recent legislation that has
been passed in Utah, SEDI stands for State
Endorsed Digital Identity, can provide a
lot of that legal foundation that we need
to make digital identity work. I don't
think it necessarily would surprise many
people at this conference, but one thing I
see differently than many is the need for
first-person identity, for identity that
is controlled by the individual rather
than provided to them by some other
organization. We've been working on self
-sovereign, decentralized identity, first
-person identity for since 2015, so 10, 11
years at this point. What has been missing
is the legal foundation that makes it
possible. I believe that what I talked
about, the legal foundation for digital
identity is not just a nice to have, but a
necessary component of a functioning
digital ecosystem where people have
dignity and the right to act for
themselves. rules rules rules rules rules
rules rules rules rules rules rules rules
rules rules rules rules rules rules